

Aiken Tine Ahac Full-Stack Developer

Full-Stack Developer
Founder
Lecturer

<u>aiken.si</u> linkedin.com/in/aahac github.com/aikenahac

ahac.aiken@gmail.com

Work experience

Aerio (Feb 2021 - Current) Co-Founder | Ljubljana, Slovenia

Aerio is a group of young tech enthusiasts and creators. We're specialized in software, audio, and media production. Our passion for technology drives us to innovate and push boundaries in our respective fields.

Skills: Leadership, Flutter, TypeScript

Website: aerio.tech

eAsistent eŠola d.o.o (Mar 2022 - Current) Software Developer | Ljubljana, Slovenia

At eAsistent I played a large role in developing the React Native application mojAsistent, a mobile app used by over 100k students.

I also played a pivotal role in creating the mobile application for parents of kindergarteners built in the Flutter framework.

I then moved to the team that was building the new mobile app for the parents of schoolchildren also built in React Native and used by over 200k parents.

At all of the projects I worked with teams of remarkable people to bring exceptional products to our customers.

Skills: React Native, Flutter, TypeScript, PHP, Laravel

Website: easistent.com

UL FRI (Nov 2023 - Apr 2024) Student Council Member | Ljubljana, Slovenia

Voted into the council in November 2023, but I had to remove myself in April 2024 after ending my education at the institution.

Skills: Communication, Planning, Management

Website: fri.uni-lj.si

Vegova Ljubljana (Sep 2023 - Jan 2024)

CS Teacher | Ljubljana, Slovenia

After completing my education at this institution, I took on a teaching role. I taught the practical class for a computer science subject that covers:

† Computer-Person interfaces † Communication with clients

* Communication with clients

* Agile principles

* Web design (HTML, CSS, JS)

* Kernel image processing

Skills: Computer Science, Teaching

Website: vegova.si

Identisoft (Jun 2022 - Jun 2022)

Software Development Intern | Braga, Portugal

Within the scope of the ERASMUS program I got to join the Identisoft company in Braga, Portugal for a month.

My task at Identisoft was to implement the MINTTI Vision Java SDK into an Android application which is used to communicate with and control the MINTTI Healthcare device.

The app was an interface to start measurements on the device, such as blood pressure, blood glucose, body temperature, SPO2 and doing an ECG with a visual representation.

Later on, I also had to use another SDK for a second application which only communicated with a ECG specific device.

Skills: Java, XML, Android

Website: identisoft.eu

Fundl (May 2021 - Nov 2021) CTO & Co-Founder | Ljubljana, Slovenia

In May 2021, myself and my team from Aerio joined the joined a small team and Co-Founded the Fundl startup. We took on the role of creating and maintaining the app, website, administration panel along with the entire system and supporting over 10k users.

My role was to oversee and collaborate on all development and communicate with other teams within the company such as design, business development, marketing,

Skills: Leadership, Flutter, NestJS, React

Website: github.com/aeriotech/onedl

YFLab d.O.O. (Jun 2019 - Aug 2021)

Lead Developer | Ljubljana, Slovenia

At the YourFlare startup, that progressed into the company YFLab d.o.o., my initial task was to create a web app for clients to use as their main tool to interact with our product. Later on, we wanted to create a mobile app, so I took on that task and started the development of our mobile app in the Flutter framework.

After being a developer at the firm for less than a year, I was presented with the task of overseeing the development, along with the creation and maintenance of the internal tools used for business processes.

Skills: Leadership, Flutter, NestJS, React

Website: linkedin.com/company/yourflare

Education

University of Ljubljana, Faculty of Computer and Information Science

2023 - 2024

Website: fri.uni-lj.si

Vegova Ljubljana 2018 - 2023

Website: <u>vegova.si</u>

Technical Skills

Front-End

- ↑ HTML/CSS/JS
- † TypeScript
 † Tailwind
- * Flutter/Dart
- * React & NextJS * React Native
- SvelteKit
- * Vue & NuxtJS
- ☆ Wordpress :(

Back-End

- † TypeScript † PHD
- NestJS
- Firebase
- Supabase
- Strapi
- Laravel
- SQL

Databases: PostgreSQL, MySQL/MariaDB,

About me

I'm a young and passionate software developer from Slovenia. I started coding when I was 7 years old and it's stuck with me ever since.

I've been working with startups since I was 15 and I am always intrigued by a new challenge.

I love working in a team, enjoy meeting new people and I am a big extrovert so I thrive in social and active teams.

Looking forward to our chat:)